bigcmobiles.in 2015-12-07

# Privacy Policy

###  Privacy Policy - General

We provide these privacy highlights for your convenience but we encourage you to review the BigC.

**Collection, Use, Disclosure, and Security of Personal Information**

  * We collect personal information when you use our services or otherwise interact with us, including information you provide, such as contact information, billing & credit information, and resumes; information that is automatically collected, such as details about use of our services and our Web pages; and information from other sources, such as credit reports and mailing lists.
  * We use personal information for various business purposes, such as to complete transactions and bill for products and services; respond to requests for service or assistance; create and improve products and services; suggest additional or different products or service; and protect our rights and property.
  * We do not sell, rent, or provide personal information to unaffiliated third-parties to market their products and services to you. We may disclose personal information to unaffiliated third-parties who complete transactions or perform services on our behalf and under certain other limited circumstances, subject to restrictions on the third-parties use of such information.
  * We use a variety of physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information and we use reasonable procedures to erase or render it unreadable when we dispose of it.

**Access and Choice**

  * You may access and modify your contact information by visiting bigcmobiles.in or by contacting Customer Service.
  * If you are a BigC customer and you manage your account online, you can change your marketing preferences by logging into your my BigC Profile.
  * You may also manage your marketing preferences by contacting Customer Service. When you dial 9966598888, the right marketing promotions and instructions will assist by us to you.

**Other Privacy Information**

  * We do not solicit children to purchase our services or products and our Web sites are not designed to attract children under the age of 13.
  * We may use cookies, Web beacons, and similar technologies.
  * BigC follows the ISO s Best Practices Guidelines for Location-Based Services. With your consent, we may provide location-based services or provide access to location information so third-parties may provide you such services.
  * Services and functionality offered through certain BigC devices are provided in conjunction with third parties, in which case personal information from your devices may be uploaded and stored on their servers.
  * When you install third-party applications on your device, you may give your consent for the third party to access certain information you have stored on your device or to access BigC network information to facilitate the application s functions.

**Policy Updates and Contact Information**

  * We may update this policy from time to time and you should refer to it often for the latest information and the effective date of any changes.
  * If we intend to use or disclose personal information in a way that is materially different from that stated in this policy at the time it was collected, we will post notice of the change on our Web site s home page for at least 30 days before we implement the change and give you an opportunity to opt-out of the proposed use.
  * If you have questions, comments, or concerns about this policy or about Bigc privacy practices, you may contact us through or using the other contact information provided in the full privacy policy.

**Privacy Policy BigC SMS**

  * BigC SMS takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.
  * What This Privacy Policy Covers? This policy covers how BigC sms treats personal information that BigC sms collects and receives? Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

**Information Collection and Use General**

  * BigC sms collects personal information when you register with BigC sms.
  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email ld, address, birth date, gender, Mobile, Location etc.
  * BigC sms automatically receives and records information about every message on our server logos.
  * We Record every Contact you register in your address book.
  * BigC sms uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, Providing More value in the form of Inserted ads in every message you send to your contacts.
